A Guide to the Papers of the Casey and Dudley Families, ca. 1923-1988
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Casey and Dudley Family Papers ca. 1923-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10974
This collection consists of ca. 9,000 items.
This collection consists of ca. 9,000 items, ca. 1923-1988, pertaining to the Casey and Dudley families. Chiefly, there are personal, business, and legal correspondence and papers of Joseph Edward Casey, Constance Marion (Dudley) Casey, and Herman Andrew Dudley. To a lesser extent, there are correspondence and papers of the Casey children and their families, Caroline Whittier Casey, Constance Louise Casey, John Casey, Joseph Edward Casey, Jr., and Jane Dudley (Casey) Kuczynski. In addition, there are also correspondence and papers of the parents of Constance Marion (Dudley) Casey, Charles Howard Dudley and Ida Louise (Ockerblad) Dudley, and their other children and their families: Bernard Francis Dudley, Charles Milo Dudley, and Robert Whittier Dudley.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited in the Library by John Casey of Charlottesville, Virginia, on August 22, 1990.
Contents List
- Correspondence of Constance Dudley Casey 1930-1977, n.d. (Box 1-4)
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Earl Smith Hewitt (1892-1959) 1934 May 25 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Henry Lane (1913-1980) 1934 Oct 26 (Box 1)
  - Arthur Dare Whiteside (1882-1960) 1934 Oct 28 (Box 1)
  - Fred Herbert Brown (1879-1955) 1935 Apr 2 (Box 1)
  - John T. Tuthill, Jr. 1935 Nov 11 (Box 1)
  - Enoch D. Fuller 1936 Feb 21, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Mary Bunce (1916-1993) 1936 Feb 29, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Charles Hoyt March (1870-1945) 1936 Mar 6, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Thomas Henry Lane 1936 Mar 20, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Enoch D. Fuller 1936 Aug 7, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Eileen Scott-Williams for Elizabeth Arden (1878-1966) 1936 Sep 30, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Mary Morris Wright artwork 1936 Dec 23, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - William Augustus Leonard (1916- ) ca. 1936, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Enoch D. Fuller telegram 1939 Feb 20 (Box 1)
  - Helen Byrne Lippmann 1945 Oct 21 (Box 1)
  - Frances Parkinson Keyes 1945 Nov 8 (Box 1)
  - Helen Gahagan Douglas (1900-1980) signed address 1945 Dec 4 (Box 1)
  - John William McCormack (1891-1980) 1945 Dec 21 (Box 1)
  - Max Gordon (1892-1978)] 1945 Mar 11, 14 (Box 1)
  - Helen Johnson Doyle Sioussat (1902- ) 1950 May 12 (Box 1)
  - Sir Frederick and Lady Dalrymple-Hamilton invitation 1950 Jul 6 (Box 1)
  - Frances Parkinson Keyes 1950 Jul 23 (Box 1)
  - Helen Byrne Lippmann 1950 Sep 29 (Box 1)
  - Howard P. Chivers (1917-1984) 1950 Nov 14 (Box 1)
  - John William McCormack 1950 Dec 19 (Box 1)
  - Helen Byrne Lippmann 1951 Jan 2 (Box 1)
  - Frances Parkinson Keyes 1951 Feb 14 (Box 1)
  - Uta [Thyra] Hagen 1951 May 21 (Box 1)
  - Kay [Murphy] Halle ca. 1951 (Box 1)
  - Marian Cannon Schlesinger (1912- ) 1952 Sep 29 ? (Box 2)
  - Frances Parkinson Keyes 1952 Nov 3, 6 (Box 2)
  - Blanche Wolf Knopf (1894-1966) 1952 Nov 6 (Box 2)
  - Mamie Doud Eisenhower (1896-1979) 1952 Dec 3 (Box 2)
  - Harold William Whitcomb (1899- ) 1952 Dec 31 (Box 2)
  - Frances Parkinson Keyes 1953 Jan 14 (Box 2)
  - Blanche Wolf Knopf 1953 May 18 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman 1953 May 26-Dec 2 (Box 2)
  - Louis B. Wright (1899-1984) 1953 Dec 9 (Box 2)
  - Harold Spivacke (1904-1977) 1953 Dec 7 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman 1954 Apr 17-May 15 (Box 2)
  - Paula Laurence Bowden 1954 Apr 18 (Box 2)
  - Ruth West 1955 Aug 9 (Box 2)
  - John Boynton Priestley (1894-1984) 1956 Jun 1 (Box 2)
  - Ruth West 1957 May 3 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman (1922- ) 1956 Aug 2, Sep 9 (Box 2)
  - Philip L. Graham (1915-1963) 1957 Dec 31 (Box 2)
  - Inaugural invitations for John F. Kennedy 1961 Jan (Box 2)
  - Edith Bolling Wilson (1872-1961) 1961 May 4 (Box 2)
  - Helen Byrne Lippmann 1961 Sep 25 (Box 2)
  - John F. Kennedy complimentary White House cards 1961 (Box 2)
  - Fleur Cowles Meyer 1962 Mar 5, May 1 (Box 2)
  - Agnes Elizabeth Ernest Meyer (1887-1970) 1962 Mar 29 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman program 1962 Oct 24 (Box 2)
  - Raphael Hillyer 1962 Dec 7 (Box 2)
  - Katharine Frost 1963 May 27 (Box 2)
  - Elizabeth Frere 1963 June 12 (Box 2)
  - Paul and Grete Koht 1963 July 31 (Box 2)
  - Lady Bird Johnson (1912- ) 1963 Dec 10 (Box 2)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. (1917- ) 1964 Oct 1 (Box 2)
  - Edmund S. Muskie (1914-1996) 1964 Nov 11 (Box 2)
  - Joseph Oliva Huot (1917-1983) 1964 Dec 2 (Box 2)
  - Lyndon Baines Johnson complimentary White House card 1964 Dec 3 (Box 2)
  - Inaugural invitation for Hubert Horatio Humphrey 1965 Jan (Box 2)
  - Lindy Boggs (1916- ) 1965 Jan 21, Feb 8 (Box 2)
  - Ruth West Herwood 1965 Feb 6 (Box 2)
  - Helen Byrne Lippmann 1965 Mar 25 (Box 2)
  - Mamie Doud Eisenhower 1965 Dec 10 (Box 2)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1965 Dec 17 (Box 2)
  - William Averell Harriman (1891-1986) 1966 Feb 2, Aug 2 (Box 2)
  - Paula Laurence Bowden and Charles Bowden 1966 Sep 20 (Box 2)
  - Bethine Church 1966 Oct 24 (Box 2)
  - Mamie Doud Eisenhower 1967 May 15 (Box 2)
  - Harding Foster Bancroft (1910-1992) 1967 Jun 16 (Box 2)
  - Frank Forrester Church (1924-1984) 1968 Jan 17 (Box 2)
  - William Howard Lawrence (1916-1972) 1968 Apr 23 (Box 2)
  - Jonathan Brewster Bingham (1914-1986) 1968 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Abigail Quigley McCarthy (1915- ) 1968 Jul 15 (Box 2)
  - William Howard Lawrence 1969 Mar
  - Mamie Doud Eisenhower 1969 May 23 (Box 2)
  - Ruth West 1969 ca. July (Box 2)
  - Jean Van Kirk Dalrymple (1902-1998) 1960s n.d. (Box 2)
  - Robert C. Hill (1917-1978) 1970 Mar 8 (Box 2)
  - William V. Shannon (1927-1988) 1970 Mar 18 (Box 2)
  - Benjamin Harrison Swig (1893-1980) 1970 Jun 24 (Box 2)
  - George McGovern mimeograph campaign letter 1971 ca. Mar (Box 2)
  - William V. Shannon 1971 Jun 30 (Box 2)
  - Christine Sadler Coe 1971 Dec 1 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman ? 1972 Jan 11 (Box 2)
  - Sinan Arif Korle (1914-1966) 1973 Jan 27 (Box 2)
  - Marya Mannes (1904-1990) 1973 Jan 29 (Box 2)
  - Kendall (Mrs. Lewis) Milestone 1973 Feb 3 (Box 2)
  - Katharine Graham (1917- ) 1973 Apr 30 (Box 2)
  - Endicott Peabody (1920-1997) 1973 May 8 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Brockman ? 1973 May 16 (Box 2)
  - Joan Fontaine (1917- ) 1973 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1973 Oct 26 (Box 2)
  - George McGovern (1922- ) 1973 Nov 17 (Box 2)
  - Piri Halasz (1935- ) 1974 Nov 14, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Gilbert Avery Harrison (1915- ) 1974 Nov 21, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Polly Shackleton (1910- ) 1974 Nov, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Collier Young (1908-1980) 1975 Jan 17 (Box 3)
  - George McGovern 1975 Feb 21 (Box 3)
  - Van Johnson (1916- ) autograph 1975 Feb 28 (Box 3)
  - Joan Fontaine 1975 Mar 8 (Box 3)
  - Ann Scoville 1975 Apr 28 (Box 3)
  - Herbert "Pete" Scoville, Jr. (1915-1985) 1975 May 21 (Box 3)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1975 Sep 8 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Warren (Mrs. John Charles) Daly 1975 Oct 13, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Eric Sevareid (1912-1992) 1975 Oct 14, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Leslie Douglas 1975 Oct 10, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Ann M. Buchwald (1920-1994) 1975 Oct 16, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Arlene Francis note (1908- ) 1975 Oct 16, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Lady Frances Ramsbotham (1919- ) 1975 Oct 16, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Christine Sadler Coe 1975 Oct 30, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Collier Young 1975 Oct 31, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Edward Thomas Folliard (1899-1976) 1975 Nov 1 (Box 3)
  - Sir Patrick Shaw (1913-1976) 1975 Nov 8 (Box 3)
  - Van Johnson 1975 Nov 8 (Box 3)
  - Irwin Shaw (1912-1984) 1975 Nov 25 (Box 3)
  - Gordon Neville Gadsby (1914- ) 1975 Dec 13 (Box 3)
  - Arlene Francis 1976 Jan 6 (Box 3)
  - Marian Cannon Schlesinger 1976 Feb 3 (Box 3)
  - Eva B. Hester 1976 Feb 15 (Box 3)
  - Stuart John Stebbins (1916- ) 1976 Feb 17 (Box 3)
  - Eleanor McGovern (1921- ) 1976 Feb 20 (Box 3)
  - Marian Cannon Schlesinger 1976 Mar 10 (Box 3)
  - Russell Baker (1925- ) 1976 Mar 19 (Box 3)
  - Van Johnson 1976 Mar 23 (Box 3)
  - Arlene Francis 1976 Mar 23 (Box 3)
  - William Orville Douglas (1898-1980) 1976 Mar 24 (Box 3)
  - Paul Hume (1915- ) 1976 Apr 16 (Box 3)
  - John Anthony Durkin (1936- ) 1976 May 3 (Box 3)
  - Eleanor Koehler 1976 May 20 (Box 3)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1976 May 28 (Box 3)
  - Pamela Averell (1920-1998) note 1976 Jun 28 (Box 3)
  - Barbara Barrie (1931- ) 1976 Jul 3 (Box 3)
  - J. Joseph Grandmaison (1943- ) 1976 Jul 16 (Box 3)
  - F. Kenneth Beirn (1910- ) 1976 Aug 7 (Box 3)
  - Van Johnson 1976 Sep 1 (Box 3)
  - Kitty Carlisle Hart (1917- ) 1976 Sep 7 & 9 (Box 3)
  - Gillis William Long (1923-1985) campaign memo 1976 Sep 30 (Box 3)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr 1976 Oct 6 (Box 4)
  - Ruth Carter Stapleton (1929-1983) 1976 Oct 25 (Box 4)
  - Lenworth M. Jacobs, Jr. 1976 Oct 28 (Box 4)
  - Andrew Vlastimir Stevovich exhibition announcement 1976 Oct 29 (Box 4)
  - Irwin Shaw (1913-1984) 1976 Nov 2 (Box 4)
  - Andrew Vlastimir Stevovich (1948- ) 1976 Nov 12 (Box 4)
  - Jane Elizabeth Cohen (1938- ) 1976 Dec 8 (Box 4)
  - Mrs. Kermit Roosevelt (1892- ) 1976 Dec 30 (Box 4)
  - Austine McDonnell Hearst (1928-1991) n.d. (Box 4)
  - Dan Huntington Fenn, Jr. (1923- ) 1977 Jan 31, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Eva B. Hester 1977 Feb 1 (Box 4)
  - Collier Young Feb 6 (Box 4)
  - Budd Schulberg (1914- ) 1977 Feb 17 (Box 4)
  - Joan Fontaine 1977 Apr 13 (Box 4)
- Correspondence of Constance Dudley Casey 1977 Jul-Dec (Box 4)
- Correspondence of Constance Dudley Casey 1978-1987, n.d. (Box 4-5)
  chronological
  - Robert Henry Barter (1913- ) 1978 Jan 29 (Box 4)
  - William Averell Harriman (1891-1986) 1978 Feb 28 (Box 4)
  - Katharine Graham 1978 Mar 21 (Box 4)
  - Ruth West 1978 Jun 5 (Box 4)
  - Sieglinde Matsuo 1978 Dec 18 (Box 4)
  - William V. Shannon (1927-1988) 1979 Mar 26 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Brockman 1979 Jul 15 (Box 4)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1979 Jul 19 (Box 4)
  - Joan Fontaine ca. 1970s (Box 4)
  - Elizabeth Midgley (1929- ) ca. 1970s (Box 4)
  - Peggy Stuart Coolidge (1913-1981) ca. 1970s (Box 4)
  - Lois Thornburg Cowles (1909-1980) ca. 1970s (Box 4)
  - John Richard Alison (1912- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
    Condolences
  - Les Aspin (1938-1995) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Lindy Boggs (1916- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Joseph Daniel Early (1933- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Myer Feldman (1917- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Robert E. Heggestad (1939- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Albert Sydney Herlong, Jr. (1909-1995) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Bill Leonard (1916-1994) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Thomas "Tip" Philip O'Neill (1912-1994) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Mrs. Kermit "Polly" Roosevelt 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - William V. Shannon 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Marc Allen White (1948- ) 1980 Sep (Box 4)
  - Helen Patton (Mrs. James Skelly) Wright (1919- ) 1980 Sep, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Mark Hill Mullin (1940- ) 1980 Oct-Dec (Box 4)
  - Eva B. Hester 1982 Mar 22 (Box 5)
  - Alfred Friendly (1911-1983) 1982 May 24 (Box 5)
  - John Stephen Monagan (1911- ) 1982 Nov 20 (Box 5)
  - C. Pinckney Deal, Jr. (1931- ) 1983 May 25 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Daniel Early (1933- ) 1983 June 30 (Box 5)
  - Edward Francis Canfield 1984 Jul 14 (Box 5)
  - John S. Monagan 1984 Oct 5 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Baird (1923-1990) 1984 Oct 11 (Box 4)
  - Harding Foster Bancroft (1910-1992) 1984 (Box 5)
  - Paula Laurence (1916- ) 1985 Jan 18 (Box 5)
  - Arthur Scheslinger, Jr. 1985 Feb 12 (Box 5)
  - Marion Frances Sullivan (1899- ) 1985 Dec 18 (Box 5)
  - Eric Sevareid 1986 Jan 23 (Box 5)
  - Paul Laurence 1986 Feb 10 (Box 5)
  - Allegra Maynard (1879-1991) 1986 Dec 3/4 (Box 5)
  - President and Mrs. Reagan official Christmas card 1986 Dec 16 (Box 5)
  - William V. Shannon 1987 Aug 13 (Box 5)
  - William V. Shannon Christmas card photograph 1987 Dec (Box 5)
  - J. Gunnar Back to Constance Dudley Casey 1933-1934 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Edward Casey to Constance Dudley Casey 1935-1972 (Box 5)
  - Draft Correspondence of Constance Dudley Casey ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 5)
- Correspondence of Joseph Edward Casey 1937-1969 (Box 6)
  - Congressional Correspondence of Joseph Edward Casey re Coal Legislation 1937 Feb-Mar (Box 6)
    - Richard M. Atkinson
    - C. Jasper Bell
    - Schuyler Otis Bland
    - Sol Bloom
    - Lewis L. Boyer
    - Frank W. Boykin
    - Ralph O. Brewster
    - James P. Buchanan
    - Francis Case
    - Emanuel Celler
    - William M. Citron
    - John J. Cochran
    - Harry B. Coffee
    - Charles L. Colden
    - William P. Cole
    - Ben Cravens
    - Fred Cummings
    - Edward W. Curley
    - Samuel Dickstein
    - Joseph A. Dixon
    - John F. Dockweiler
    - Matthew A. Dunn
    - Charles R. Eckert
    - William J. Fitzgerald
    - Hampton P. Fulmer
    - T. Alan Goldsborough
    - Joseph W. Gorman (telegram)
    - Lex Green
    - Arthur H. Greenwood
    - Paul R. Greever
    - U. S. Guyer
    - Vincent F. Harrington
    - Edward J. Hart
    - Franck R. Havenner
    - John P. Higgins
    - Frank E. Hook
    - Virginia E. Jenckes
    - Dewey E. Johnson
    - Sam H. Johnson
    - Wade H. Kitchens
    - Leo Kocialkowski
    - Charles H. Leavy
    - William Lemke
    - Louis Ludlow
    - John Luecke
    - Warren G. Magnuson
    - John L. McClellan
    - Charles F. McLaughlin
    - James M. Mead
  - Abe Murcock
    - John R. Murdock
    - George D. O'Brien
    - Jerry J. O'Connell
    - John M. O'Connell
    - Edward Leo O'Neill
    - Vincent L. Palmisano
    - Quintin Paredes
    - Alfred N. Phillips, Jr.
    - A. Willis Robertson
    - Will Rogers
    - A. J. Sabath
    - Byron N. Scott
    - Paul W. Shafer
    - Martin F. Smith
    - Henry B. Steagall
    - Karl Stefan
    - Hatton W. Sumners
    - Albert Thomas
    - Andrew J. Transue
    - Jerry Voorhis
    - Otha D. Wearin
    - Zebulon Weaver
  - Congressional Papers of Joseph Edward Casey 1937-1941 (Box 6)
    campaign material; "Speech made on the Day the United States Declared War on Japan"
  - Correspondence of Joseph Edward Casey 1937-1958 (Box 6)
    - Inaugural invitation for Franklin D. Roosevelt 1937 Jan (Box 6)
    - Ted Patrick 1943 Dec (Box 6)
    - letters re Crucifix and Rosary blessed by Pope Pius XII 1946 (Box 6)
    - John W. McCormack 1946 May 23 (Box 6)
    - Marquis W. Childs 1947 Jun 24 (Box 6)
    - Daniel H. Coakley 1947 Jul 10 (Box 6)
    - J. M. Elizalde 1947 Jul 17 (Box 6)
    - Louis Denfeld 1947 Jul 17 (Box 6)
    - Hubert Horatio Humphrey 1948 Jun 10 (Box 6)
    - statement re American Overseas Tanker Corporation 1951 Mar 28 (Box 6)
    - Orra L. Stone with autobiographical sketch on Joseph E. Casey 1957 May 11 (Box 6)
    - Ted Patrick 1957 Dec 12 (Box 6)
    - Eric Sevareid ca. 1958 Jan (Box 6)
    - Eddie O'Connor 1958 Sep 24 (Box 6)
    - John Cowles 1958 Oct 11 (Box 6)
    - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. 1958 Nov 7 (Box 6)
    - Eddie O'Connor 1959 Apr 8 (Box 6)
    - John W. McCormack 1959 Apr 17 (Box 6)
    - Anthony C. Mitchell 1959 Apr 24 (Box 6)
    - Robert E. L. Eaton 1959 Jun 8 (Box 6)
    - Alex Wylie 1959 Jul 10 (Box 6)
    - James Roosevelt 1959 Oct 22 (Box 6)
    - Theodore Francis Green 1960 Jan 21 (Box 6)
    - George C. Sweeney 1960 Jun 2 (Box 6)
    - Thurman Arnold 1960 Jul 13 (Box 6)
    - George D. Aiken 1961 Mar 3 (Box 6)
    - Alfred Friendly 1961 Jul 17 (Box 6)
    - Luther W. Youngdahl 1962 May 2 (Box 6)
    - James McC. Truitt 1962 Oct 4 (Box 6)
    - John Charles Daly 1962 Dec 13 (Box 6)
    - George C. Sweeney 1963 May 26 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence of Joseph Edward Casey 1964-1969 (Box 6)
    - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr 1964 Jan 6 (Box 6)
    - Edward Bennett Williams 1964 Feb 19 (Box 6)
    - Barbara Bolling 1964 Sep 14 (Box 6)
    - letters re election night party, including letters from Dick Russell, Samuel Taylor, John Kenneth Galbraith, Catherine (Mrs. Al) Capp, Harriet (Mrs. James Gerald) Crowley 1964 Oct-Nov (Box 6)
    - William V. Shannon 1968 Jan (Box 6)
    - Ann (Mrs. David Brinkley) 1968 Sep 23 (Box 6)
    - John P. Philbin 1968 Oct 30 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence of Joseph Edward Casey with Michael and Mary McGuire 1937-1966 (Box 6)
- Papers of Constance (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey 1915-1986, n.d. (Box 6-11)
  - Academic Planner/Appointment Book of Constance (Dudley) Casey 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Address Book of European and Latin American Contacts n.d. (Box 6)
  - Affairs: Washington's Weekly Review 1936 Feb-Jun (Box 6)
  - Biographical Data on Constance (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey 1915-1976 (Box 6)
  - Diary entries of Constance Dudley Casey 1964, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Diary entries of Constance Dudley Casey 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Diary entries of Constance Dudley Casey 1981, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Financial Papers of Constance (Dudley) and Joseph E. Casey 1937-1986 (Box 7)
  - John F. Kennedy 1944-1963 (Box 7)
  - William M. Mayer: Aurosol—Correspondence 1958-1962 (Box 7)
  - William M. Mayer: Aurosol—Papers 1958-1961 (Box 7)
  - William M. Mayer: Claim 1943-1953, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - William M. Mayer: Claim—Trial Documents 1943-1954 (Box 7)
  - Playbills and Programs kept by Constance Dudley Casey 1934-1985 (Box 8)
  - Political Miscellaneous kept by Constance Dudley Casey 1932-1986 (Box 8)
  - Printed re Constance (Dudley) and Joseph E. Casey 1936-1980, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Printed re Religion and Temperance 1929-1932 (Box 7)
  - Printed re Schools 1951-1980 (Box 8)
  - Properties of Constance (Dudley) and Joseph E. Casey 1946-1986 (Box 8)
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey 1923-1925 (Box 8)
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey, Stoneleigh School 1930-1931, 2 folders
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey, Stoneleigh School 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey, Dartmouth College 1933-1934 (Box 9)
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey, University of Wisconsin 1933-1934 (Box 9)
  - School Papers of Constance Dudley Casey, Smith College 1933-1936 (Box 9)
  - School word-book and advanced exercises 1924, n.d. (Box 9)
  - School essays of Constance Dudley Casey 1970-1972, 2 folders
  - School notes of Constance Dudley Casey 1972 (Box 9)
  - School essays of Constance Dudley Casey 1972, 2 folders
  - School essays of Constance Dudley Casey 1973, 2 folders
  - School essays of Constance Dudley Casey 1975, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Francis Cardinal Spellman 1946 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: Chapters and Miscellaneous Writings for his book 1975-1978 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: Correspondence with Bill Brown 1976 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: Correspondence with Joseph E. Casey 1944-1971 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: Correspondence with Joseph E. Casey and Constance Dudley Casey 1974-1976 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: FBI and related data 1973-1978 (Box 10)
  - William C. Sullivan: "Hoover" by Robert Collins based upon Sullivan's book "The Bureau" 1980 (Box 10)
  - Washington Heart Association Women's Board Directory 1965-1967 (Box 10)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club 1950 (1970-1976) (Box 10)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club: Calendars and Newsletters 1955 (1974-1976) 1984 (Box 10)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club: Speeches, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club: Speeches 1961 (Box 11)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club: Speeches 1965-1978, n.d. (Box 11)
  - World-Wide Tankers, Inc. 1947-1948, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - World-Wide Tankers, Inc.: Corporate Records 1948 (Box 11)
- Correspondence and Papers of the Casey Children 1944-1988, n.d. (Box 11-12)
  - Caroline Whittier Casey 1958-1984, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Constance Louise Casey 1950-1967, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - John Casey 1945-1988, n.d., 5 folders (Box 12)
  - John Casey: First Day Covers belonging to 1952-1954 (Box 12)
  - John Casey: Publication of An American Romance 1976-1977 (Box 12)
  - Joseph Edward Patrick Casey, Jr. 1953-1986, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Jane Dudley (Casey) and Pedro-Pablo Kuczynski 1944-1985 (Box 13)
- Correspondence of Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1920-1972, n.d. (Box 13-14)
  - Constance Marion (Dudley) Casey to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1920-1954, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Constance Marion (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1955-1969, 2 folders
  - Casey Children to their Grandparents, Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1955-1970 (Box 13)
  - Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley to Constance Marion (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey 1946-1972, 5 folders (Box 14)
  - Ida Louise (Ockerblad) Dudley to Charles Howard Dudley 1934 Mar-Apr, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Bernard Francis Dudley to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley to Herman Andrew Dudley 1934 (Box 14)
  - Robert Whittier Dudley to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1933 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence of Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1933-1964, n.d. (Box 14)
- Papers of Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1913-1976, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Papers re Dudley Estate 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Papers re Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1913 (1956-1973) (Box 14)
  - Papers re Interlaken at Croydon, New Hampshire 1932-1963, n.d. (Box 14)
- Correspondence of Herman Andrew Dudley 1931-1978, n.d. (Box 15-17)
  - Constance Marion (Dudley) Casey to Herman Andrew Dudley 1935-1959, n.d. (Box 15)
  - Joseph Edward Casey to Herman Andrew Dudley 1950-1975 (Box 15)
  - Herman Andrew Dudley to Constance Marion (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey 1934-1972, 13 folders (Box 15)
  - Herman Andrew Dudley to Constance Marion (Dudley) and Joseph Edward Casey 1973-1978 (Box 16)
  - Herman Andrew Dudley to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1933-1935, 14 folders (Box 16)
  - Herman Andrew Deadly to Ida Louise (Ockerblad) and Charles Howard Dudley 1938-1970, n.d., 10 folders (Box 17)
  - Correspondence of Herman Andrew Dudley 1931-1934 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence of Herman Andrew Dudley 1935 (Box 17)
    [letters re search for employment; resume]
  - Correspondence of Herman Andrew Dudley (1936) 1946 (Box 17)
    [letters re employment with Jersey Railways Advertising Company; Phi Kappa Psi Fraternity letters; letters re Reserve commission]
  - Correspondence of Herman Andrew Dudley: V. I. P. 1952-1976 (Box 17)
    [Warren Beatty; Jimmy Carter; Bennett Cerf; Gardner Cowles; Olivia de Havilland; Arlene Francis; John Gielgud; Oscar Hammerstein, II; Abdol Hosseim Hamzavi; Rahim Hirad; Hubert Horatio Humphrey; Alfred A. Knopf; Van Johnson; Frederic March; Richard Nixon; Cyril Ritchard; Eleanor Roosevelt; Rosalind Russell; Arthur Sclesinger, Jr; Wallis Simpson, Duchess of Windsor; Harry S. Truman; Earl Warren]
  - Invitations sent to Herman Andrew Dudley 1954-1976, n.d. (Box 17)
- Papers of Herman Andrew Dudley 1929-1984 (Box 18)
  - Dartmouth College Papers of Herman Andrew Dudley 1929-1934, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Economic Papers kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1931-1934 (Box 18)
  - Economic Papers re the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1947-1948 (Box 18)
  - National Recovery Administration Papers kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1933-1936 (Box 18)
  - National Recovery Administration Printed kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1933-1935, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Papers re Herman Andrew Dudley 1934-1979 (Box 18)
  - Papers re Herman Andrew Dudley Memorial 1980-1984 (Box 18)
  - Playbills kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1953-1954 (Box 18)
  - Programs for Orchestra Concerts kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1953-1954 (Box 18)
  - Programs and other Brochures kept by Herman Andrew Dudley 1933-1957 (Box 18)
- Correspondence and Papers of the Dudley Family 1941-1986, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Bernard Francis and Betty Dudley 1941-1952 (Box 19)
  - Bernard Francis and Anne Dudley 1963-1985, n.d., 2 folders (Box 19)